Guide to the Annie Dillard Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- January 2011 Acquisition, 1960s-2010; 7; 12.17 linear feet (18 boxes)
  - Computer Media, 2000s
    - 4/21/03: a.doc (i.e. address book) a olda, 2011-ycal-41606-0072; 1 (Box 74)
- May 2013 Acquisition, circa 1987-2012; 8; 1.5; (4 boxes)
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Purchased from Annie Dillard on the Danford N. Barney, Jr. Fund, 2013.
  - Typescripts, notes, notebooks, news clippings, correspondence and research material, circa 1987-2012 (Box 75)
  - Typescripts, notes, notebooks, news clippings, correspondence and research material, circa 1987-2012 (Box 76)
  - News clippings, photograph, and artwork, circa 1987-2012 (Box 77)
  - Electronic media, 1990s-2010s; 2 3.5 inch floppy disks and 5 CDs
    Box 78 (computer disks): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - [no label information], 2013-ycal-32-0001; 1 (Box 78)
    - a l vision vita rosie lastdr~1.txt supplement Oct 16, 01 11/21, 2013-ycal-32-0002; 1 (Box 78)